Narrator: 1
M: This check-in queue is really slow!
F: Don’t worry.
It’ll start moving soon.
Narrator: optimist
M: This check-in queue is really slow!
F: I know.
We’ll miss the flight.
Narrator: pessimist
F: Let’s drive to the restaurant.
M: We’ll never find anywhere to park.
Narrator: pessimist
F: Let’s drive to the restaurant.
M: Yes, it’ll be quicker.
Narrator: optimist
M: I’ve lent my brother some money.
F: I’m sure he’ll pay you back.
Narrator: optimist
M: I’ve lent my brother some money.
F: You won’t see it again.
Narrator: pessimist
F: I’m taking my driving test tomorrow.
M: It’ll go well, you’ll see.
Narrator: optimist
F: I’m taking my driving test tomorrow.
M: You won’t pass.
Narrator: pessimist
M: I’m selling my old laptop online.
F: You’ll sell it easily.
Narrator: optimist
M: I’m selling my old laptop online.
F: Nobody will buy it.
Narrator: pessimist
F: Hooray! We’re in the final!
M: Yes! But we’ll lose.
Narrator: pessimist
F: Hooray! We’re in the final!
M: Yes! I’m sure we’ll win!
Narrator: optimist
M: I’m having Japanese classes next week.
F: That’ll be interesting!
Narrator: optimist
M: I’m having Japanese classes next week.
F: You’ll never learn it.
Narrator: pessimist
F: We’re going to see the film in English.
M: You won’t understand a word.
Narrator: pessimist
F: We’re going to see the film in English.
M: You’ll love it.
And it’ll be good practise.
Narrator: optimist